妈的王八蛋！
You motherfucker!
Fuck!
王八蛋 选叉的混蛋！
Motherfucker! Fucking X bastard!
兔崽子 王八蛋！
Damn you!
Fuck you! You fucking loser!
- 去死吧 王八蛋 你个废物！
- 王八蛋！
- You fucker!
- Fucking asshole! Die!
去死吧 兔崽子！
王八蛋！
《鱿鱼游戏 2》
SQUID GAME 2
集名：《第七集：是敌是友》
EPISODE 7
FRIEND OR FOE
宣布淘汰人员
The following players
have been eliminated.
230号
Players 230, 268,
268号
299号
299, 331, and 401.
331号
401号
淘汰
End of list.
什么情况？
What's going on?
选圆圈的各位！
Listen, Team O!
我们…
We…
我们在卫生间 那些选叉的混蛋
When we were in the bathroom,
those fucking X bastards
tried to kill all of us!
攻击我们 要弄死我们！
我的朋友也死了 我们这边
They killed some of us,
including my friend--
- 死了好几个
- 你少放屁
Bullshit.
是你们先开始的
You're the ones who started it.
妈的
Damn it.
那些混蛋先威胁我们这边的人！
They threatened one of the people
on our side!
他们为了在重新投票中获胜
对我们进行攻击！
They attacked us to win the second vote!
没错！
That's right!
喂
Hey.
是你们先把我们这边的人杀了
You killed one of us first.
把我们弄死 明天投票他们就赢了！
You were trying to win the vote
by killing us!
放屁 我们这边也有人死了
Fuck you. You killed some of us too.
你们想杀了我们这边所有的人
我们能坐视不管吗？
Did you think we would
just let you kill the rest of us?
所以
So?
到底哪边死的人多？
Which side lost more people?
什么情况？
What?
来 各位！
All right, everyone!
Let's count the numbers!
清点一下剩下的人！
对 没错！
Yeah, that's right!
Let's count ourselves! Come on down!
看看我们这边有多少人 过来！
我们也数一下 大家都过来！
Everyone! Gather round!
所有人全都来这边！
We need everyone down here! Come on!
- Get down here now!
- Gather round!
快点过来 快！
全都过来！
- Come on!
- Get down here!
大家快点过来！
- 排成一排！
- 聚过来
- Gather round!
- Form a line!
- 全都聚过来
- 排成一排！
- 全都过来！
- 过来！
- Please come down!
- Form a line!
- 来 排成一排！
- 过来！都下来！
船长？
- Captain?
- Huh?
这个时间 您在那里干什么呢？
What are you doing here?
哦 那个…
Oh, well…
那不是我的无人机吗？
Isn't that my drone?
啊？啊 这个？
What? Oh, this?
不是 我睡不着 在找东西
Well, I was looking for something
because I couldn't sleep,
偶然看到的…
and I just stumbled across it.
您动了这个吗？
Did you do something?
没有 我只是看看
No, I was just looking.
这东西能飞上天 感觉太神奇了
I'm fascinated by
how this thing can fly in the sky.
来 我都看好了
All right. I'm done now.
看着真神奇
It's so fascinating.
哎哟 一股酒味
You reek of alcohol.
快点回去睡觉吧 嗯？
Go get some sleep now, okay?
等一下！
Stop!
你是什么人？
Who are you really?
混蛋！
You son of a bitch!
谁在那里？
Who's there?
Choi, is that you?
崔理事
是我 朴船长
It's me, Captain Park.
船长
Captain, I thought you were asleep.
What are you doing out here?
雨下这么大
您不睡觉 跑来外面做什么？
It's pouring down.
睡不着觉 翻来覆去的
I couldn't sleep.
I was tossing and turning,
好像听到外面有什么声音
then I heard some noise.
我也听到了
I heard it too.
我好像听到有人尖叫
然后听到了咣当的声音
I think I heard someone scream
and some thuds after that.
所以我也跑出来查看了
That's why I came out to take a look.
应该是海浪拍击甲板的声音
I think it was the waves hitting the deck.
你看 乱七八糟的
Look at the mess.
啊 这样啊
Oh, you're right.
暴风雨来的时候
出来很危险 快进去睡吧
It's dangerous out here in the rain.
Go back inside and get some sleep.
我睡不着 海浪晃动太厉害了
The boat's rocking so much.
I can't really sleep.
那也应该稍微睡一会儿
Still, you've got to wake up early.
Try to get some sleep.
清晨又要开始新的一天了
不睡明天就受罪了
Or you'll be exhausted tomorrow.
41、42、43、44、45
41, 42, 43, 44, 45,
46,
47.
死了三个人
Three dead.
- 确定吗？
- 数了三次呢
Are you sure?
I counted three times.
他们呢？
What about them?
42、43、44、45
42, 43, 44, 45, 46, 47, 48.
46、47、48
我们这边死了两个人
Two people died on our side.
死了五个人 两个人是我们这边的
Two out of five.
That means they lost three people.
也就是说他们那边死了三个人
那么
Then we have a better shot
at winning the vote tomorrow.
明天投票 对我们这边更有利
喂 48对47
Hey, it's 48 against 47.
只要我们不改变心意
再投票一次就赢了！
As long as we don't change our minds,
we'll win by one vote!
赢了！
Yes!
- 我们赢了
- 明天就能出去了
- We'll win.
- We can get out of here tomorrow.
重要公告
Attention, please.
Lights out in 30 minutes.
三十分钟后将会熄灯
请各位玩家回到自己的位置
All players, please return to your beds
and prepare for bedtime.
- 准备就寝
- 来
各位千万不能改变心意
Listen. You cannot change your minds.
重新进行投票
We have to win the second vote
and get out of here tomorrow. All right?
明天一定要出去 知道吗？
不用担心 一定要出去
Don't worry. We're determined to get out.
对 我们这一次真的出去吧
That's right.
We really have to get out now.
Yes, let's do this.
出去吧
All right.
Let's go to sleep now, shall we?
来 我们现在睡觉吧？
配送队伍已出发
The delivery team has set out.
物品状态呢？
How are the goods?
这次全都是最好的
In top condition this time.
11号呢？
And Number 011?
我也告诉过那个女的了
现在没有问题了
That bitch is behaving.
Won't be a problem anymore.
一定要监视她到最后
Keep watching her carefully.
是
Yes, sir.
准备
Get ready.
稍后将开始特别游戏
The special game will begin momentarily.
请各位管理员、士兵和劳工
Managers, soldiers, and workers,
迅速前往指定游戏场所
please move to your designated locations.
重复一遍
Let me repeat.
稍后将开始特别游戏
The special game will begin momentarily.
请各位管理员、士兵和劳工
Managers, soldiers, and workers,
迅速前往指定游戏场所
please move to your designated locations.
距离熄灯还有20分钟
Lights out in 20 minutes.
请各位玩家准备就寝
All players, please prepare for bedtime.
那些选圆圈的人感觉有点奇怪呢
Those bastards are acting suspicious.
感觉成群结队在谋划一些什么
It looks like they're up to something.
不管怎样 过了今晚 再次进行投票
Whatever those idiots do,
once we win the vote tomorrow,
他们就全完了 一群混蛋
it'll all be over.
- 妈的
- 但真的没问题吗？
You think we'll be okay?
刚才在卫生间 真不是开玩笑的
They say things were really crazy
in the bathroom earlier.
熄灯之后
Once the lights go out,
那边会攻击我们这边
people on the other side will attack us.
真的吗？
Really?
我们死了 他们投票会赢
Because if they kill us, they'll be able
to win the vote and increase the prize.
奖金也能增多
那怎么办？
So what do we do?
我们先进行攻击吧
Let's attack them first.
那边的人
They're probably thinking
we'll just wait for the second vote.
会觉得我们只会等着明天重新投票
我们反其道行之
We can use it to our advantage.
熄灯之后 我们先攻击他们
We'll attack them first
once the lights go out.
对啊 还是我们先动手吧
That's right.
It'd be better to attack them first.
我们这边女士和老年人很多
We have more women
and elderly on our side.
对我们进行攻击 对我们很不利
If we get attacked,
we'll be at a disadvantage.
还不如我们先偷袭 胜算还更大一点
Attacking them first
would give us a better chance of winning.
- 我也赞成
- 不行
- I agree.
- We can't do that.
无论如何也要想办法出去啊
But we have to get out of here.
你不是也说嘛
You said it yourself.
现在开始 冷静已经没用了
Staying calm won't get us anywhere now.
那我们也不能互相残杀啊
That doesn't mean
we should kill each other.
这样就正中那些人下怀
That's exactly what they want us to do.
“那些人”？
"They"?
创造这个游戏的那些人
The ones who created this game.
还有监视我们玩这个游戏的那些人
The ones who watch us play.
如果我们要战斗
If we're going to fight someone,
it should be them.
应该是跟那些人战斗
那些人在哪里呢？
Where are they?
在那上面
Up there.
在楼上
On the upper levels
控制这个游戏的人和设备都在那里
are the rooms they control the games from.
戴黑色面具的是他们的队长
The man in the black mask is their leader.
抓到那个人
Once we capture him, we'll be able to win.
我们就能赢
要怎么战斗？
How are you going to fight them?
那些人有枪
They have guns.
各位武装士兵 请前往指定场所
All armed soldiers,
please move to your designated locations.
稍后将开始特别游戏
The special game will begin momentarily.
我们也要用枪战斗
We'll fight them with guns too.
哪里有枪？
But we don't have any.
抢他们的就行
We'll take their guns.
从面具人手里抢吗？
From those masked men?
太危险了
That's too dangerous.
就算我们能抢来几把枪
他们比我们人数多太多了
Even if we manage to take a few guns,
we'll still be outnumbered.
那么就在这里
What then?
整夜互相残杀
Are you going to kill each other all night
and hope you survive?
希望自己能活下来吗？
这真的是你希望的吗？
Is that what you want, Young-il?
会有…
Do we…
胜算吗？
stand a chance?
偷袭就有胜算
We do if we catch them off guard.
尤其是那些人
Out of everyone,
不会预料到我们会先进行攻击
they're the ones
who would least expect us to attack first.
这次
This is
是我们能让整个游戏都结束
our last chance
to end these games once and for all.
最后的机会
要怎么把枪抢过来？
How are you going to take their guns?
今天晚上
Once the fight begins tonight,
打起来之后
就会有机会
we'll have our chance.
距离熄灯还有五分钟
Lights out in five minutes.
萨诺斯这个傻瓜
Thanos, that fucking asshole.
太目中无人了 混蛋
That son of a bitch
treated me like a fucking idiot.
李明基
Myung-gi.
一会儿熄灯之后马上藏起来
When the lights go out, hide.
不管发生什么事情都不要出来
No matter what happens, don't do anything.
嗯
Okay.
还有 你把血擦擦吧
And wipe that blood off.
距离熄灯还有十秒
Lights out in ten seconds.
十、九
Ten,
nine,
八
eight,
七
seven,
六
six,
五
five,
四
four,
三
three,
二
two,
一
one.
熄灯之后
Once the lights go out,
静悄悄移动到床下面
get under the bottom beds quietly.
不能让那些想攻击我们的人
You must not get caught
by those planning to attack us.
先发现我们
安静！
Shut up!
去死吧！
Die!
不要！
走开 混蛋 滚开！
大家在各自的位置上等待
We have to hide until the fight ends.
一直到战斗结束
绝对不能卷入战斗
Don't get caught up in the fight.
这样一来
But that would put people on our side
at quite a disadvantage.
对我们选叉这边很不利
我们全都退出战斗 人数也比他们多
Without us in the fight,
they'll be outnumbered.
我知道
I know.
但如果我们卷入战斗
But if we fight with them
我们中如果有几个人死亡或者受伤
and some of us end up dead or injured,
机会就全没了
it will ruin our entire plan.
如果我们这边比现在人数还少
We can't beat those bastards
with a lower headcount.
那就没办法赢过那些人
所以为了大义
Are you suggesting that
就要承受小的牺牲吗？
we make a small sacrifice
for the greater good?
如果错过这次机会
If we miss this opportunity,
会让更多人牺牲
the sacrifice will be even greater.
就算现在会有牺牲…
Even if it takes a sacrifice…
这次也一定要让游戏结束
we must put an end to this game now.
那么我就
In that case,
按照你的意思做吧
I'm with you.
斗争不会持续太久
The fight won't last long.
那些人看到玩家全都死亡或者受伤
Because if all of us end up hurt or dead,
这样就没办法进行下一场游戏
这是他们不希望见到的
there can't be a next game,
and they wouldn't want that.
世美姐
Se-mi.
你个混蛋婊子
You fucking bitch.
妈的！
Fuck!
兔崽子！
You goddamn bastard!
贱人！
You fucking bitch!
喂 你说我混蛋吗？
You think you're better than me?
镇压！
Suppress!
准备
Prepare.
镇压
Suppress.
开灯之后 士兵会进来
Once the lights come on,
the soldiers will come
to settle the situation.
开始整顿现场
手举起来 退后
Hands up. Get back.
他们会先控制在打斗的人
They'll try to break up the fight first.
放下武器 举起手
Drop your weapon. Hands up.
根本不会在意死的人
They won't pay attention to the dead.
他们会确认
倒下的淘汰人员身份信息…
- They will scan our trackers…
- Check the IDs of the dead.
检查淘汰人员
…进行扫描
…to identify us.
我们就在这个时候伺机行动
That'll be our window.
大虎！
Dae-ho!
全体人员撤退 关门
Have everyone retreat and close the gate.
撤退
Retreat.
停止！射击停止！
Stop! Hold fire!
所有人停手！
Everyone, hold fire!
手放在头上！
Hands above your head!
跪下！
On your knees!
你们这些混蛋！
You goddamn bastards!
不行！
No!
让开！
Move! Do you not see this?
你眼里看不到这些吗？
那些混蛋根本不是人
They are not human.
他们像蛀虫一样 被钱蒙蔽了双眼！
They're like goddamn vermin
blinded by money!
我们把枪抢过来 不是为了杀他们的
This is not what we took these guns for.
我们如果也这样
就跟那些面具人没有区别了
If we do this, we'll be no different
from those masked men.
各位！
Everyone!
不用害怕
Don't be scared.
Gather round, please!
大家都过来！
没关系 出来吧
It's okay to come out.
我们无意伤害各位！
We're not trying to hurt you!
- 从死的面具人身上…
- 大家全都出来！
- Get the guns and ammo from the dead.
- Come on! I have something to say!
- …收集枪和弹仓吧
- 我有话要说！
所有士兵集合！
Gather all soldiers.
请所有士兵带上武器
All soldiers, please move
to the assembly point with your weapons.
前往集结地点
重复一遍
Let me repeat.
请所有士兵带上武器
All soldiers, please move
to the assembly point with your weapons.
前往集结地点
各位
Everyone.
现在我们
We will now
要去楼上的
head up to the masked men's headquarters.
那些面具人的大本营
去抓关押我们的混蛋
We'll capture the ones who captured us,
结束这个游戏
put an end to this game,
让他们为自己犯下的错付出代价
and make them pay.
会使用枪的人
Anyone who knows how to use a gun
愿意跟我们一起去的人
请走到前面来
and wishes to join us,
please step forward.
各位
Hey.
我知道各位害怕
I know you're scared.
我也非常害怕
I'm scared too.
但如果现在不行动
But this may be
可能就再也没有
大家一起活着出去的机会了
our last chance
to make it out of this place alive.
我们一起战斗
Fight with us
一起回家吧
so we can go home together.
所有人一起
All together.
我要一起战斗
I'll fight with you.
请过来
Come on.
- 我也一起去
- 过来
I'll join you too.
Come join us.
来 拿着枪
好 请拿上两个弹仓
请大家各自确认手中的枪支和弹药
Please check your guns and ammo.
每人拿一个对讲机
Let's take one radio each.
为了幸运 我们使用七号频道
We'll use channel 7, the lucky number.
刚才谢谢你
Thank you for earlier.
等出去了
You can buy me a soju when we get out.
你请我喝杯烧酒
各位注意
Attention.
这是MP5冲锋枪
This is the MP5, a submachine gun.
首先
First, if you press this lever
in the middle and pull the magazine,
把中间这个控制杆按下 拔出
就可以把弹仓分离
it comes off like this.
然后把这个调整杆往下压
是连续发射
If the selector switch is down,
it's set to full auto mode.
往上抬就是单次发射
Up is single-fire mode.
我们现在剩下的弹仓不多
We don't have many magazines,
so set it to single-fire mode.
请一定要调整到单次发射模式
最后 把弹仓装上
Lastly, insert the magazine,
把拉手往上拉 再放手 就会上膛
pull the handle, and then release it.
That's how you load it. Are we clear?
都听懂了吗？
是！
- Yes.
您怎么这么了解枪？
How do you know so much about guns?
我以前是特种兵的中士
I was a sergeant first class
in the ROK Special Forces.
摘掉
Take it off.
这个也摘掉
Take that off too.
哎呀
Good God.
你做这种工作 你父母知道吗？
Do your parents know
what you're doing here?
带我们去你们队长那里
Take us to your captain.
各位玩家 睡觉时间到了
All players, it is bedtime now.
请立刻回到宿舍
Please return to your quarters
immediately.
不回宿舍
Otherwise,
you will be eliminated from the game.
将会被淘汰
重复一遍
Let me repeat.
各位玩家
All players, it is bedtime…
- 睡觉时间到了
- 啊 这个声音
I think I'll be hearing this voice
in my dreams. Don't you?
回家做梦都会听到吧？
- 请现在…
- 是啊
…立刻回到宿舍
Please return to your quarters
immediately. Otherwise…
不回宿舍…
趴下！
Get down!
一点方向！
One o'clock!
掩护我！
Cover me!
- 掩护！
Cover!
停止射击！
Hold fire!
大家都没事吧？
Is everyone okay?
- 是
- 是 没事！
- Yes.
- Yes, I'm okay!
那我们走吧！
All right, then. Let's go up!
绝对不能让他们靠近管理区域
Do not let them get close
to the management area.
还要走多远？
How much farther?
真是这条路吗？
Is this the right way?
在那个尽头转弯 有管理区入口
The entrance to the management area
is around that corner.
那上面就是控制室
The control room is right above it.
快走！
Move it, then.
等一下
Wait.
你在做什么？
What are you doing?
想要通过 必须有面具
I need my mask to pass security.
我去找找管理区入口！
I'll go look for the management area!
能找到吗？要我跟你一起去吗？
Will you be able to find it?
Should I come?
我跟正倍一起去！
I'll go with Jung-bae.
请你在这里想办法拖延一下时间！
I need you to buy us some time!
正倍 走吧！
Jung-bae, let's go.
等我！
Wait up!
给你！
Here!
子弹很宝贵！
Don't waste your ammo like that!
You'll quickly run out!
那样用的话 坚持不了多久！
身份确认完毕
Identity confirmed.
你为什么不跟零一来 要带我来？
Why did you have to bring me
instead of Young-il?
毕竟你是我朋友
Because you're my friend.
这小子 紧急情况就承认是朋友了
You only say that when you're in a jam.
我们进入管理区域了
We're in the management area.
我们上去看看
We'll make our way up.
正倍 这些家伙裤兜里也有弹仓
They have magazines in their pockets.
现在要往哪边走？
Which way should we go?
那些家伙来的方向
The way they came.
守住通往控制室的台阶！
Guard the stairs to the control room!
我们在这里待着不是办法
我们也上去吧！
This isn't getting us anywhere!
Let's follow them to the upper level!
都没有计划 全部冲上去
可能会被包围！
We might get surrounded
if we move together without a plan!
我们再稍微等一下
等到他们在对讲机里说
Let's wait until
they find the control room!
找到控制室再上去！
所有人确认一下弹仓！
Everyone! Check your magazines!
我就剩一半了！
I'm down to half.
我都没剩一半了
I've got less than half.
妈的 我也是！
Same!
我还剩三分之二
I've got two-thirds left.
我全都用掉了！
I'm almost out!
我没有了！
Mine is empty!
我也没多少了！
I'm almost out too!
零一 大虎 有人在听吗？
Young-il, Dae-ho. Can you hear me?
你说！
Go ahead!
从这里过去应该就是控制室了
哎呀 我们两个人不太行！
I think we're right below
the control room!
But we need backup and more ammo.
派点支援过来 再拿点弹药！
这边弹药也不够了！
We're running out of ammo too!
宿舍士兵尸体的口袋里
应该有剩的弹仓
There should be spare magazines
in the soldiers' pockets in our quarters.
把那些带过来就行了！
Go get them!
知道了！
Got it!
都听到了吧？
Did you hear that? They need backup!
上面需要支援！
先过去三个人 剩下的守在这里！
Three of us will go,
and the rest will stay!
取到弹仓 然后就加入大家！
Join us once you get the magazines!
谁跟我一起走？
Who wants to go with me?
- 我去！
- 我也过去！
I'll go!
Me too!
走吧！
Let's go!
我去宿舍取弹仓！
I'll go get the magazines!
我会尽快赶回来 请一定要坚持住！
I'll come back as soon as I can,
so just hold on until then!
贤珠！
Hyun-ju!
我过去！
I'll go!
我没有子弹了
I… I'm out of ammo.
你认识路吗？
Do you know the way?
认识
Yes.
我们一路过来的时候
把摄像头打掉了 顺着那个走就行
We destroyed the cameras on the way.
Follow them.
好！
Okay.
你带上这个
Take this. You might run into
the masked men on the way.
路上有可能会遇到面具人
谢谢
Thank you.
我们会掩护你 快走！
I'll cover you. Go!
掩护！
Cover him!
裤兜里的弹仓
Magazines in pockets.
大虎！
Dae-ho.
大虎 能听到我说话吗？
弹仓拿到了吗？
Can you hear me?
Where are those magazines?
能听到 大哥
Yes, brother. I'm on my way to get them.
我正在往那边走
好 大虎 全靠你了！
All right, Dae-ho! We're counting on you!
好 大哥 交给我吧 我现在就去！
Yes, you can count on me, brother!
I'll be there soon!
正倍 掩护我一下
Jung-bae, cover me.
- 你要干什么？
- 我去拿弹仓
What are you going to do?
Get their magazines.
不行 太危险了！
No, that's too dangerous.
没有多少弹药了
I'm almost out of ammo.
如果被他们发现了 会直接杀过来
If they notice, they'll close in on us.
要坚持到大虎过来 我们需要弹仓
We need more magazines
to hold out until Dae-ho gets here.
奇勋 快点！
Gi-hun, hurry up!
行了 快点过来！
Hurry up and get back here!
弹仓
Magazines…
裤兜里的弹仓
Magazines in pockets.
那个人干什么？
What's up with him?
我也不知道
I'm not sure.
大虎
Dae-ho, what happened?
怎么样了？
你怎么一个人回来了？
Why are you back by yourself?
弹仓
Magazines.
请帮我找到这些家伙裤兜里的弹仓！
Get the magazines
from those bastards' pockets. Hurry!
- 快点！
- 哦 好
Oh, okay.
没事吧？
Are you all right?
没事 擦伤了一点
I'm fine. It's just a graze.
如果你比我先死 我饶不了你
If you die before me, I'll kill you.
不用担心 我会比你活得久
Don't worry. I'll be sure to outlive you.
奇勋！
Gi-hun! Did you find the control room?
找到控制室了吗？
应该就在上面 但这边上不去
I think it's right up there,
but we can't go this way.
你们找找其他路径
I want you to find another way.
我上来的时候看了一眼结构
I did a quick scan of the layout here.
后面肯定有路过去
I'm sure there's a way to go around them.
你们两个在这里吸引那些人的注意
I want you guys
to keep their focus on you.
我从后面攻击 过去找找
We'll hit them from behind.
好
Okay.
等一下
Wait.
Here, take this.
带上这个
你用得上
You're going to need it.
你真的没事吗？
Are you sure?
大虎会带着弹仓过来
Dae-ho will be back with more.
全都翻出来了
This was all we could find.
妈的 他怎么还不来？
Damn it, what's taking him so long?
不会是忘记路了吧？
Do you think he got lost?
大虎 能听到吗？
Dae-ho, can you hear me?
大虎 你在哪里？能听到吗？
Where are you? Can you hear me?
弹仓怎么样了？拿到过来了吗？
Did you find the magazines?
Are you on your way?
大虎 请回答！
Dae-ho, answer me.
大虎！
Dae-ho, are you there?
你在吗？
大虎 拜托你回答！
Dae-ho, please answer me!
- 大虎 回答！
- 坚持不住了
Dae-ho! Answer me!
We can't hold out much longer.
We need those magazines now.
我们现在就需要弹仓
应该是发生什么事情了
Something must've happened.
I'll go down and check.
我过去看看！
拜托你了
Please do.
掩护我！
Cover me!
奇勋 找到了
Gi-hun, we found it.
你先攻击他们 引起注意
Start attacking and draw their attention.
然后我们从后面攻击
Then we'll hit them from behind.
好 知道了！
Okay, got it!
零一 怎么样了？
已经发动攻击了吗？
Young-il, what's going on?
Are you attacking?
奇勋 对不起
Gi-hun, I'm sorry.
完蛋了
It's all over.
我们也中枪了
They got us too.
零一 发生什么事了？
Young-il, what happened?
Are you all right?
你没事吧？
零一
Young-il.
零一 回答我！
Young-il! Answer me!
零一！
Young-il!
开始整理
Start wrapping things up.
大虎！
Dae-ho!
大虎 你在哪里？
Dae-ho, where are you? Dae-ho!
大虎 大…
大虎！
Dae-ho!
大虎
Dae-ho.
怎么样了？
What happened?
对不起
I'm sorry.
弹仓呢？
The magazines?
对不起
I'm sorry.
对不…
I'm…
对不起
I'm sorry.
所有人趴下！
Get down on the floor!
不要！
No.
不能这样送死
You can't die like this.
面具人正在过来！
They're moving!
正在往我们这边来！
They're coming this way!
往下面撤退吧
We should retreat.
这边的路也堵死了
This side is blocked as well.
各位玩家 睡觉时间到了
All players, it is bedtime now.
请立刻回到宿舍
Please return to your quarters.
不回宿舍…
Otherwise you will be eliminated
from the game.
- …将会被淘汰
- 不要！
No. Don't!
重复一遍
Let me repeat.
各位玩家 睡觉时间到了
All players, it is bedtime now.
请立刻回到宿舍
Please return to your quarters.
- 我们投降吧
- 不回宿舍…
Otherwise…
Let's surrender.
…将会被淘汰
怎么都要想办法活下来
We need to survive somehow.
先遣队 能听到吗？
Advance team, do you copy?
没有弹药了
We're out of ammo.
我们会投降
We're surrendering.
饶了我…
Please don't kill--
求你饶了我
Please don't kill me.
我女儿病得很重
My daughter is very sick.
投降
I surrender.
456号
Player 456.
扮演英雄有意思吗？
Did you have fun playing the hero?
看好了
Look closely
你扮演英雄的结果
at the consequences
of your little hero game.
是怎样的
奇勋
Gi-hun.
不要！
No!
正倍！
Jung-bae!
正倍
Jung-bae…
390号
Player 390, eliminated.
淘汰
字幕翻译：李江珊
Subtitle translation by: Yoonjung Song